
var questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Lattice + motif = ?  ",
        answer: "Crystal",
        options: [
            "Composite",
            "Crystal",
            "Polymer",
            "None of the above",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Ceramics having nuclear applications can be used as ",
        answer: "Both a & b",
        options: [
            "Controls",
            "Moderators",
            "Both a & b",
            "None of the above",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "According to pascals principle, hydrostatic pressure inside the water in a dam or a swimming pool ",
        answer: "Increases with depth",
        options: [
            "Decreases with height",
            "Increases wirh height",
            "Increases with depth",
            "Decreases with depth",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which of the following is not the assumption made in the derivation of bernoulis equation?",
        answer: "The flow is compressible",
        options: [
            "The fluid is ideal",
            "The flow is compressible",
            "The flow is steady",
            "The flow is irrotational",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "When a body placed over a liquid, it will sink down if gravitational force is",
        answer: "Is more than the upthrust of the liquid",
        options: [
            "Equal to the upthrust of the liquid",
            "Is less than the upthrust of the liquid",
            "Is more than the upthrust of the liquid",
            "None of the above",
        ],
    },
   {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Gas laws are applicable to?",
        answer: "Gases alone and not vapours",
        options: [
            "Gases as well as vapours",
            "Gases alone and not vapours",
            "Gases and steam",
            "Gases and vapours under certain circumstances",
        ],
    },
{
        numb: 7,
        question: "Gases law can be fully determined by ?",
        answer: "1st law of thermodynamics",
        options: [
            "1st law of thermodynamics",
            "2nd law of thermodynamics",
            "3rd law of thermodynamics",
            "4th law of thermodynamics",
        ],
    },
{
        numb: 8,
        question: "The dotted lines represent?",
        answer: "Hidden edges",
        options: [
            "Projection line",
            "Hidden edges",
            "Centre line",
            "Hatching line",
        ],
    },
{
        numb: 9,
        question: "The internal angle of regular pentagon is _______ degree?",
        answer: "108",
        options: [
            "72",
            "108",
            "120",
            "150",
        ],
    },
{
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which of the following is not included in the forming and shaping process?",
        answer: "Broaching",
        options: [
            "Rolling",
            "Forging",
            "Sheet forming",
            "Broaching",
        ],
    },
];